<ZT2Strings>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:VulnerableAnimalsintro">Vulnerable Animals Adoption Program</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:VulnerableAnimalsoverview">
	Captive breeding is a strong indication of a zoo's ongoing commitment to wildlife conservation. The major donors backing your 
	zoo are so committed to conservation that they have put a restriction on your ability to adopt animals from other 
	facilities. They are insisting that you develop a thriving breeding and active adoption program so that you can 
	offer animals to other facilities.  
	<p/>
	Meet the advanced needs of your animals to encourage reproduction. Don't let your animals become too crowded in their 
	exhibits. Put extra animals up for adoption to other facilities but make sure you keep enough of an animal stock 
	so that you can continue to maintain a growing and thriving animal community.  
	<p/>
	You will receive an adoption fee for each animal adopted by another facility and all funds raised through the 
	adoption program will allow you to better provide for special diets, animal enrichment toys and comfortable 
	homes for your animals.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:VulnerableAnimalsoverviewshort">
        Captive breeding is a strong indication of a zoo's ongoing commitment to wildlife conservation. Develop a thriving breeding 
        and active adoption program so that you can offer animals to other facilities.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:VulnerableAnimalsSuccessoverview">
	Your breeding program has successfully added to the world's vulnerable animal population. You have had enough animal births
	to support placing your animals up for adoption to other facilitiesand in doing so you have contributed to the 
	conservation of these important animals.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:VulnerableAnimalsFailureoverview">
	You have neglected to keep enough mixed gender animals to maintain a breeding program. Unfortunately you have no way
	to breed your animals to support any sort of adoption drive. Contrary to the wishes of your zoo's major donors, you would
	have no choice now but to adopt additional animals.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:VulnerableAnimalsresult">Animal Adoption program a success!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:VulnerableAnimalsBreeding">
      	Breed your animals and offer extra animals up for adoption. You must put at least 6 animals up for adoption but make 
      	sure that you have at least as many animals as when you started.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:VulnerableAnimalsBreedingone">
      	You have successfully placed one animal up for adoption!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:VulnerableAnimalsBreedingtwo">
      	You have successfully placed two animals up for adoption!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:VulnerableAnimalsBreedingthree">
       You have successfully placed three animals up for adoption!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:VulnerableAnimalsBreedingfour">
      You have successfully placed four animals up for adoption!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:VulnerableAnimalsBreedingfive">
       	You have successfully placed five animals up for adoption!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:VulnerableAnimalsBreedingsix">
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:VulnerableAnimalsBreedingOK">
      	Your exceptional breeding program has allowed you to place six animals up for adoption!
      	Your donors are satisfied that you've made a positive impact on 
      	conservation by supplying other facilities through this adoption program. 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:VulnerableAnimalsBreedingFailed">
      	Oh no! You no longer have enough of an animal stock to continue your breeding program. Your donors are very disappointed.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:EndangeredAnimalsintro">Endangered Animals Species Survival</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:EndangeredAnimalsoverview">
	The birth of any baby animal is always a momentous occasion but the captive breeding of endangered animals 
	is an important, proactive way of ensuring species survival. 
	<p/>
	Guests particularly enjoy seeing baby animals. When the species is endangered, it makes even more of an impact 
	and guests are more likely to make generous donations when they view these special babies. 
	<p/>
	Meet the advanced needs of your Mountain Gorillas, Red Pandas and Snow Leopards to encourage their 
	reproduction. Achieve $2000 in donations for each of these endangered animals.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:EndangeredAnimalsoverviewshort">
        The birth of any baby animal is always a momentous occasion but the captive breeding of endangered animals 
	is an important, proactive way of ensuring species survival. Do your part to encourage the reproduction of several
	species of endangered animals.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:EndangeredAnimalsSuccessPart1overview">
	Your breeding program has made a superb contribution to the survival of several endangered species. Guests really 
	enjoy viewing baby animals and when those babies are endangered, it's even more appealing. The 
	extra appeal of these babies is likely to increase your donation revenue. 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:EndangeredAnimalsSuccessPart2overview">
	You have had excellent results obtaining additional revenue from donations. This additional income will allow 
	your zoo even more flexibility to fund new exhibits, improve animal accomodations or expand the amenities available to your
	guests.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:EndangeredAnimalsresult">Endangered animals thriving!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:EndangeredAnimalsBreedGorilla">
	Breed your Mountain Gorillas.      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:EndangeredAnimalsBreedRedPanda">
      	Breed your Red Pandas.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:EndangeredAnimalsBreedSnowLeopard">
      	Breed your Snow Leopards.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:EndangeredAnimalsBreedGorillaOK">
      	Great! You've successfully bred Mountain Gorillas!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:EndangeredAnimalsBreedRedPandaOK">
      	Great! You've successfully bred Red Pandas!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:EndangeredAnimalsBreedSnowLeopardOK">
      	Great! You've successfully bred Snow Leopards!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:EndangeredAnimalsBreedingFailed">
        Oh no! You no longer have enough of an animal stock to continue your breeding program. 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:EndangeredAnimalsFailureoverview">
	You have neglected to keep enough mixed gender animals to maintain a breeding program. Unfortunately you have no way
	to breed your animals to support a conservation program for endangered animals.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:EndangeredAnimalsGorillaDonations">
      	Now that you have a Mountain Gorilla baby, achieve $2000 in donations for your Mountain Gorillas.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:EndangeredAnimalsRedPandaDonations">
      	Now that you have a Red Panda baby, achieve $2000 in donations for your Red Pandas.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:EndangeredAnimalsSnowLeopardDonations">
      	Now that you have a Snow Leopard baby ,achieve $2000 in donations for your Snow Leopards.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:EndangeredAnimalsGorillaDonationsOK">
      	You have received at least $2000 in donations for your Mountain Gorillas.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:EndangeredAnimalsRedPandaDonationsOK">
      	You have received at least $2000 in donations for your Red Pandas.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:EndangeredAnimalsSnowLeopardDonationsOK">
      	You have received at least $2000 in donations for your Snow Leopards.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:SecondGenerationintro">Second Generation Animals</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:SecondGenerationoverview">
	Breeding animals in captivity is a difficult venture that many zoos strive to add to their list of 
	accomplishments. Successfully breeding second-generation animals is even more challenging. Establish a 
	thriving breeding program where any of your animals breed second generation animals, and your zoo will be added to 
	the list of the select few who have successfully supported multiple breeding generations.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:SecondGenerationoverviewshort">
        Breeding animals in captivity is a difficult venture that many zoos strive to add to their list of 
	accomplishments. Successfully breeding second-generation animals is even more challenging. Can your zoo 
	be one of the few than can boast of this accomplishment?
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:SecondGenerationSuccessoverview">
	Few facilities can boast that they have successfully bred second generation animals. You have been added to a 
	list of the select few who can make this claim. Your notoriety in the world of zoos is certain to be widespread 
	and the births of your animal additions have made headlines around the world.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:SecondGenerationFailureoverview">
	You have neglected to keep enough mixed gender animals to maintain a breeding program and achieving the select status
	of breeding multiple generations of animals is out of your grasp.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:SecondGenerationresult">A thriving animal community!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:SecondGenerationBreeding">
      	Successfully breed any of your animals such that the offspring of animals bred in your zoo are also successfully bred.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:SecondGenerationBreedingZebraOne">
      	Your Common Zebras have produced their first offspring!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:SecondGenerationBreedingZebraTwo">
      	The offspring of your Common Zebras have produced a second generation of Zebras!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:SecondGenerationBreedingLemurOne">
      	Your Lemurs have produced their first offspring!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:SecondGenerationBreedingLemurTwo">
      	The offspring of your Lemurs have produced a second generation of Lemurs!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:SecondGenerationBreedingChimpOne">
      	Your Chimpanzees have produced their first offspring!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:SecondGenerationBreedingChimpTwo">
     	The offspring of your Chimpanzees have produced a second generation of Chimpanzees!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:SecondGenerationBreedingOK">
      	Congratulations! Very few facilities can say they have successfully bred second generation animals. You have been added to a list of the select few that have. 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvival:SecondGenerationBreedingFailed">
      	Oh no! You no longer have enough of an animal stock to continue your breeding program. 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvivalLabels:SpeciesSurvivalshort">Conservation Programs</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvivalLabels:VulnerableAnimalsS1">Animal Adoption Program</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvivalLabels:VulnerableAnimalsS1short">Animal Adoptions</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvivalLabels:EndangeredAnimalsS2">Animal Conservation</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvivalLabels:EndangeredAnimalsS2short">Animal Conservation</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvivalLabels:SecondGenerationS3">Second Generation Animals</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SpeciesSurvivalLabels:SecondGenerationS3short">Second Generation</LOC_STRING>   
   
</ZT2Strings>
