<ZT2Strings>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:ZookeeperTrainingintro">Zookeeper Training</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:ZookeeperTrainingoverview">
	You have been given a great opportunity to take over a small local zoo but before completely entrusting the 
	animals into your care, the current owner wants to be sure that you understand that animals have individual 
	biome needs. He has provided you with three animals that need to be placed in their appropriate biome exhibit area.
	<p/>
	Each animal can be found in a crate near the front entrance of your zoo. When you select the crate, the information panel indicates what kind of animal is inside. You can pick up the crate and move it like any other object.  To release an animal from its crate, click the Uncrate Animal button that is on the animal's information panel. Once an animal is released, you will be able to use the information tabs to access additional information about the animal.
	<p/>
	You will need to move and release each crated animal into its appropriate exhibit.

      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:ZookeeperTrainingoverviewshort">
        You have a great opportunity to take over a small zoo but need to prove that you understand that animals have individual 
	biome needs. Make sure each animal is moved into its appropriate biome exhibit area.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:ZookeeperTrainingSuccessoverview">
	Excellent work! It's clear that you understand that animals require different habitats in order to thrive in a zoo environment.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:ZookeeperTrainingFailureoverview">
	Animals are living creatures and need the appropriate care in order to survive. Without receiving proper care in a timely fashion, animals can become
	sick. 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:ZookeeperTrainingresult">A thriving animal community!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:ZookeeperTraininggoal">
      	Release each animal from its crate and place it in the appropriate biome exhibit area.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:ZookeeperTraininggoalOK">
      	Excellent! Your animals feel right at home in their new exhibits.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:ZookeeperTraininggoalFailed">
      	Oh no! An animal has died! You will need to place them into their exhibits in a more timely fashion. 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:StartUpintro">Zookeeper Training</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:StartUpoverview">
	There are a number of steps to creating a thriving zoo for the animals and 
	for the guests. In your start-up zoo, you'll need to take things one step at a time to build your 
	facility into a popular destination spot.
	<p/>
	Your fledgling zoo has been given a pair of Common Zebras. Guests enjoy watching animals interact with each 
	other and these two animals should help draw guests into your zoo. 
	<p/>
	Create an exhibit area of a suitable biome to meet the environment needs of your Common Zebras and 
	meet their basic hunger and thirst needs.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:StartUpoverviewshort">
        There are a number of steps to creating a thriving zoo for the animals and 
	for the guests. In your start-up zoo, you'll need to take things one step at a time to build your 
	facility into a popular destination spot.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:StartUpFailedoverview">
	Unfortunately things haven't worked out quite as planned in your zoo start-up. It's important to provide
	care for your animals in a timely manner.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:StartUpGoalOne">
      	Create a suitable exhibit for your Common Zebras.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:StartUpGoalOneA">
      	Meet the basic hunger and thirst needs of your Common Zebras.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:StartUpGoalOneOK">
      	Excellent! Your new animals have fit right into their new environment.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:StartUpGoalOneAOK">
      	Great! Your Common Zebras' food and water needs have been met.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:StartUpSuccessoverview">
	Now that you have additional guests coming to your zoo, you need to provide more in the way of amenities. Although 
	you have some basic food amenities available, not all of your guests want to eat the same food. You will be able 
	to place a greater variety of buildings by performing research to obtain the building plans. Research the 
	Hamburger Food Stand and the Sparkling Water Drink Stand to obtain new building options and increase your guest 
	amenities.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:StartUpGoalTwo">
      	Research the Hamburger Food Stand and Sparkling Water Drink Stand and add these buildings to your zoo. 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:StartUpGoalTwoOK">
      	Great! Now your guests have more options to choose from!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:StartUpSuccessTwooverview">
	Although your zoo is small, it's getting off to a great start. Word of mouth will help spread the news but 
	it would be better if you could obtain some publicity for your new zoo. A journalist has offered to print 
	an article about your zoo and has asked for a photograph of your Common Zebras.  The latest buzz in all the 
	animal publications are the benefits of providing enrichment objects to stimulate animals. The journalist 
	would like 2 pictures - one of your two Common Zebras interacting with each other, and another that shows at 
	least one of them interacting with an enrichment object.
	<p/>
	You will need to research the scratching post enrichment object in order to take the required photograph.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:StartUpGoalThree">
      	Provide two photographs to help promote your zoo.  Photograph a Common Zebra grooming another Common Zebra and 
      	photograph a Common Zebra using the scratching post enrichment object.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:StartUpGoalThreeOK">
      	The photos were fabulous. Many people have just learned that you have these new animals available in your zoo!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:StartUpSuccessThreeoverview">
	With your increased notoriety, you have been offered two more animals on temporary loan. You have been given 
	two Jaguars for your park and will be able to keep them for two months.  For the animal loan to be successful, 
	you will need to create a suitable environment with enough space for them to exercise, provide them with adequate 
	food and water, and ensure that they are able to satisfy their need to rest. Providing shade with trees is often 
	a good idea.
	<p/>
	You can find your Jaguars in crates near the front gates.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:StartUpGoalFour">
      	Create a new exhibit for your Jaguars and satisfy all of their basic needs.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:StartUpGoalFourOK">
      	Excellent! Your Jaguars are doing great!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:StartUpGoalFourFailed">
        Unfortunately it's time to return the animals and they never really felt at home in their new environment.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:StartUpSuccessFouroverview">
	Everything is progressing smoothly. The article about your Common Zebras has had a positive impact on 
	guest attendance. Your Jaguars are increasing popularity even more. Now that your zoo is becoming well 
	known, you will have greater opportunities to get even more interesting animals.
	<p/>
	The next step in superior animals care is to meet the animals' advanced needs. Animals that meet these 
	higher level needs are more likely to reproduce and provide you additional animals for your exhibits.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:StartUpGoalFive">
      	Meet the advanced needs of your Jaguars.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:StartUpGoalFiveOK">
      	Excellent progress! Your Jaguars are totally content! Continue along these lines and you'll be well on your way to 
      	achieving a thriving zoo.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:StartUpGoalFiveFailed">
        Unfortunately it's time to return the animals and you were unable to meet their advanced needs.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:StartUpSuccessFiveoverview">
	You've accomplished all of the basic steps to building a successful zoo. Always remember that animals have individual
	needs and do best when all their needs are being met. Keep an eye on your guests as they will enjoy watching happy 
	animals. If your animals are unhappy, your guests will become upset.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:StartUpresult">You zoo is ready to grow!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:BeyondStartUpintro">Donation Revenue</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:BeyondStartUpoverview">
	By following the basic steps of obtaining new animals, meeting their basic needs, providing better 
	amenities for your guests, and enhancing your exhibits to provide for animals' advanced needs, 
	you will increase your zoo fame.  As your zoo fame increases, so does the guest traffic through 
	your zoo.  Happy animals make for happy guests... and happy guests, among other things, like to make 
	donations.  
	<p/>
	With the experience you've gained creating a new start-up, the next step is to transition into 
	a successful growth facility. Expand on this basic zoo to obtain growth in zoo fame, and guest 
	traffic. A final measure of your success will come from donations obtained in your zoo.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:BeyondStartUpoverviewshort">
        With the experience you've gained creating a new start-up, the next step is to transition into 
	a successful growth facility. Expand on this basic zoo to obtain growth in zoo fame, and guest 
	traffic. A final measure of your success will come from donations obtained in your zoo.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:BeyondStartUpSuccessoverview">
	With a solid grasp of the basics of creating a thriving zoo, a successful zoo design future lies in 
	front of you. Use these basics to take on bigger and bigger challenges from restoring 
	dilapidated facilities to making your mark with conservation efforts.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:BeyondStartUpresult">Donation Revenue growing! </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:BeyondStartUpgoal">
      	Obtain $5000 in guest donations.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTraining:BeyondStartUpgoalOK">
      	Well done! Your zoo has all the markings of becoming a 5 star facility!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTrainingLabels:ZookeeperTrainingshort">Zookeeper in Training</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTrainingLabels:ZookeeperTrainingS1">Zookeeper in Training</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTrainingLabels:ZookeeperTrainingS1short">Zookeeper in Training</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTrainingLabels:StartUpS2">Start-Up Zoo</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTrainingLabels:StartUpS2short">Start-Up Zoo</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTrainingLabels:BeyondStartUpS3">Beyond Start-Up</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZookeeperTrainingLabels:BeyondStartUpS3short">Beyond Start-Up</LOC_STRING>   
   
</ZT2Strings>
