<ZT2Strings>


   <zoopedia_beaverlodge>
         <entry>Beaver Lodge</entry>
         <text>
            <img src="entities/objects/shelters/BeaverLodge_Shelter/BeaverLodge_Shelter_icon.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            <p/>
            Beavers construct the beaver lodge from sticks, twigs and branches placed in their exhibit.  
	             <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_beaver:entry">
	                <u>
	                   <color r="0" g="0" b="255">Beavers</color>
	                </u>
	             </a>             
             enter the lodge by swimming into the entrance.
         
         </text>
         
   </zoopedia_beaverlodge>

   
   <zoopedia_cubbingden>
         <entry>Cubbing Den</entry>
         <text>
            <img src="entities/objects/shelters/CubbingDen_Shelter/CubbingDen_Shelter_icon.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            <p/>            
	       A cubbing den is a warm, quiet enclosure that certain female animals will 
	       use to give birth. It is used by 
	             <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_grizzly:entry">
	                <u>
	                   <color r="0" g="0" b="255">bears,</color>
	                </u>
	             </a>	       
	        
	             <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_panda:entry">
	                <u>
	                   <color r="0" g="0" b="255">pandas</color>
	                </u>
	             </a>	       
	        and 
	             <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_gorilla:entry">
	                <u>
	                   <color r="0" g="0" b="255">gorillas.</color>
	                </u>
	             </a>	       
	        Animals that give birth in 
	       cubbing dens are less likely to become ill. 
	       
	       

         </text>
         
   </zoopedia_cubbingden>
   
   <zoopedia_elephanthouse>
            <entry>Elephant House</entry>
            <text>
            <img src="entities/objects/shelters/ElephantHouse_Shelter/ElephantHouse_Shelter_icon.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            <p/>                               
               This large, roomy concrete structure is designed to accommodate the 
               particularly large mass of the elephant
            
            </text>
            
   </zoopedia_elephanthouse>
   
   <zoopedia_nestbox>
            <entry>Elevated Nest Box</entry>
            <text>
            <img src="entities/objects/shelters/ElevatedNestBox_Shelter/ElevatedNestBox_Shelter_icon.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            <p/>               
               The elevated nest box is a small house-like shelter mounted on a tall pole, which 
               satisfies the needs of animals who like to nest above the ground.
            
            </text>
            
   </zoopedia_nestbox>
   
   <zoopedia_giraffehouse>
            <entry>Giraffe House</entry>
            <text>
               
               This tall building is designed to accommodate the extra height requirements of the 
               tall giraffe.
            
            </text>
            
   </zoopedia_giraffehouse>
   
   <zoopedia_groundnest>
            <entry>Ground Nest</entry>
            <text>
            <img src="entities/objects/shelters/GroundNest_Shelter/GroundNest_Shelter_icon.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            <p/>                
               A ground nest, which is really nothing more than a large pile of leaves, is a comfortable 
               resting place for many animals.
	       <p/>
	       For many animals, including the gorilla, building a nest is a highly instinctual activity.

            
            </text>
            
   </zoopedia_groundnest>
   
   <zoopedia_treestump>
            <entry>Hollow Tree Stump</entry>
            <text>
               
               Both the giant panda and the red panda consider a tall, hollow tree stump to be a very 
               natural and inviting form of shelter. Guests enjoy seeing animals use shelters that 
               more closely represent natural habitats.
            
            </text>
            
   </zoopedia_treestump>
   
   <zoopedia_concreteshelter>
            <entry>Concrete Shelters</entry>
            <text>
               
		The large concrete shelter is a man-made structure that provides a restful environment 
		and maximum protection for animals that prefer to sleep in an enclosure, including 
		tigers, cheetahs, and most bears. Up to 2 animals may sleep in the small concrete 
		shelter and up to 4 animals are accomodated by the large concrete shelter.
            
            </text>
            
   </zoopedia_concreteshelter>
   
   
   <zoopedia_rockcave>
            <entry>Rock Cave</entry>
            <text>
               
               The large rock cave, which includes a hole in the roof to ensure adequate ventilation, 
               provides a natural habitat for animals, including the polar bear and cheetah, who prefer 
               a dark, enclosed resting environment. The small cave accomodates 2 animals, 
               and the large cave holds 4.
            
            </text>
            
   </zoopedia_rockcave>
   
   <zoopedia_snowyrockcave>
            <entry>Snowy Rock Cave</entry>
            <text>
               
               The large snowy rock cave, which includes a hole in the roof to ensure adequate 
               ventilation, provides a natural habitat for animals, including the penguin and the 
               polar bear, who are comfortable in frigid, dark, and enclosed resting environments. 
               The small cave accomodates 2 animals, 
               and the large cave holds 4.
            
            </text>
            
   </zoopedia_snowyrockcave>   
   
   <zoopedia_stable>
            <entry>Stables</entry>
            <text>
               
               A wooden building contains stalls bedded with straw, providing a comfortable enclosure for hooved animals.  
               An exterior overhang provides shade and protection from the elements. The small stable has 2 stalls and the 
               large stable has 4.
            
            </text>
            
   </zoopedia_stable>   
   
   
   <zoopedia_woodenshelter>
            <entry>Wooden Shelters</entry>
            <text>
               
               This man-made structure provides protection for animals that prefer to sleep in an enclosure.
               Up to 2 animals may sleep in the small wooden shelter and up to 4 animals can sleep in the 
               large wooden shelter.
            
            </text>
            
   </zoopedia_woodenshelter>   
   
   
   <zoopedia_raisedsleepingplatform>
            <entry>Raised Sleeping Platform</entry>
            <text>
               
               A raised platform with wooden ramps allows animals to walk up and sleep in a more protected position off 
               the ground.
            
            </text>
            
   </zoopedia_raisedsleepingplatform>   
   
   
   <zoopedia_shadestructure>
            <entry>Shade Structure</entry>
            <text>
               
               This simple structure provides animals with a place to seek shelter from the sun.
            
            </text>
            
   </zoopedia_shadestructure>   
   
   
   <zoopedia_sleepingbasket>
            <entry>Sleeping Basket</entry>
            <text>
               
               A basket primarily used by primates. One large animal or two small ones can fit comfortably into the basket. 
               The basket can be made more restful if bedding material is placed in the exhibit.  
               Bedding material will deteriorate over time.
            
            </text>
            
   </zoopedia_sleepingbasket>   
      
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   </ZT2Strings>