<ZT2Strings>
   
   
   <WildlifeMagChallengetext>
   	
   	<PHWildlifeMagPhotos>Wildlife Magazine</PHWildlifeMagPhotos>
   	<PHWildlifeMag>
		Wildlife Magazine is running a photo contest and will pay $2000 per photograph for each 
		photo they run in their magazine. The contest ends in 2 months. They have requested photos of specific 
		animals. At the end of the time period, Wildlife Magazine will pay you for each photo you have 
		been able to successfully take.  
   	</PHWildlifeMag> 
   	<PHWildlifeMagShort>
   		Provide the following photographs:
   		<p/>
   		*  A single photo containing three Common Zebras.
   		<br/>
   		*  A photo containing 2 Greater Flamingoes and a Hippopotamus.
   		<br/>
   		*  A Nile Crocodile in the water.
   		<br/>
   		*  A Red Kangaroo thumping its tail.
   	</PHWildlifeMagShort>   	
   	<PHWildlifeMagFailure>
   		The contest period has ended and unfortunately you did not provide any of the photos requested by
   		Wildlife Magazine. Better luck next time!
   	</PHWildlifeMagFailure>
	<PHWildlifeMagFailureShort>
		Unfortunately you were unable to provide any of the photos reqeusted by Wildlife Magazine.
   	</PHWildlifeMagFailureShort> 
   	<PHWildlifeMagPartialSuccess>
   		The contest period has ended. Wildlife Magazine has paid you for the photos you were 
   		able to take.
   	</PHWildlifeMagPartialSuccess>   	
	<PHWildlifeMagFullSuccess>
		Wildlife Magazine loves your photos! They also recognize that achieving such a unique collection
		of pictures in such a short time was no small accomplishment and have presented you with the 
		Wildlife Magazine Amateur Photographer Award. Congratulations on your achievement!
	</PHWildlifeMagFullSuccess>
   	<PHWildlifeMagSuccessShort>
   		Your photos were a big hit with Wildlife Magazine.
   	</PHWildlifeMagSuccessShort>

   	<stt_ThreeZebras>Take a single photo of a three Common Zebras.</stt_ThreeZebras>
   	<stt_TwoFlamingoesandHippo>Take a photo containing 2 Greater Flamingoes and a Hippopotamus.</stt_TwoFlamingoesandHippo>
   	<stt_CrocinWater>Take a photo of a Nile Crocodile in the water.</stt_CrocinWater>
   	<stt_KangarooTailThump>Take a picture of a Red Kangaroo thumping its tail.</stt_KangarooTailThump>
   	

   	
   	
   	
   	

   </WildlifeMagChallengetext>
   
   
</ZT2Strings>
